ethnicdukaan.com 2016-05-03

# Buy Indian Dresses Online – Traditional Indian Women Wear, Designer Saris, Wedding Lehengas, Salwar Kameez, Kurtis, Bridal Wear and Handloom Sarees

We are Ethnicdukaan.com, a service provided by Aashirvad Group from Kolkata, West Bengal, India. In this Privacy Policy, references to “you” mean any person submitting any data to us or our agent or the site.

If you have any comments or suggestions, we would be pleased to receive them at our Kolkata address or by email.

Data protection is a matter of trust and your privacy is important to us. We shall therefore only use your name and other information which relates to you in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect information if it is relevant to our dealings with you.

We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.

You can visit the site and browse without having to provide personal details. During your visit to the site you remain anonymous and at no time can we identify you unless you have an account on the site and log on with your user name and password.

**Keeping your Information Secure**

'Ethnic Dukaan.com' is purely adhered to protect and respect your privacy. So, if you're asked about your personal information, like your postal address, email, phone, payment information etc, it's only to keep you in regular communication with us, before, during, and after your purchase. We do not divulge your personal information to any third party without your consent.

Your card information is used only by EBS and then by Visa/MasterCard/Diners to verify your credentials and authorize your transaction.

**Information that we collect**

We need information in order to allow you to go ahead with placing your order for a product. We may use that data to process payment for the product and deliver the product to you. We also use that data to inform you when the product is about to be delivered.

We may pass your name and address on to a third party in order to make delivery of the product to you (for example to our courier or supplier).

We may also share your data with our franchisor. You further authorize the franchisor to use this information to sell products to you, directly or indirectly.

We may also use your data in order to manage the Site, collect payment from you, enable you to subsequently use parts of the Site, detect any fraud or Site abuses, send you information relevant to the Site or our products, and in case we have any queries. Payments that you make through the Site will be processed by our company Aashirvad Group, a company registered in India.

You must only submit to us or our agent or the site information which is accurate and not misleading and you must keep it up to date and inform us of changes.

Your actual order details may be stored with us and you may access this information by logging into your account on the site. Here you can view the details of your orders that have been completed, those which are open and those which are shortly to be dispatched and administer your address details, bank details and any newsletter to which you may have subscribed. You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties.

We shall not share any of your personal information with third parties without your explicit consent. We only use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. We view protection of your privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and your information is one of our most important assets. We store and process your information on computers located in the India that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices As we follow a structured secure platform for our costumers We have third parties to verify and certify our privacy principles. If you object to your information being transferred or used in this way please do not use the site.

Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your personal information that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

Deal of the Week: In case you avail the ‘Deal of the week’, we may use your name and location on our website as you would be one of the lucky customers to have gotten the deal!

**Credit Check and Fraud Prevention**

We use standard and authorized payment services and our Credit Check and Fraud Prevention policies are aligned to these companies. All disputes would be handled by Kolkata courts.

**Other uses of your personal information**

We may also send you other information about the site, our other websites, our products, sales promotions, our newsletters, and about us, anything relating to other companies in our group or our business partners. If you would prefer not to receive any of this additional information as detailed in this paragraph (or any part of it) please “unsubscribe” by following the un subscription process or by sending an email. Kindly note that unsubscribing from one medium does not automatically lead to un subscription from the other. Within 7 working days (days which are neither (i) a Saturday nor Sunday, or (ii) a public holiday anywhere in India) of receipt of your instruction we will cease to send you information as requested. If your instruction is unclear we will contact you for clarification.

**Third Parties and Links**

We may pass your details to other companies in our group. We may also pass your details to our agents and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in our Privacy Policy. For example, we may use third parties to assist us with delivering products to you, to help us to collect payments from you, to analyze data and to provide us with marketing or customer service assistance. We may exchange information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We may transfer our databases containing your personal information if we sell our business or part of it. Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, we shall NOT sell or disclose your personal data to third parties without obtaining your prior consent unless this is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or unless we are required to do so by law. The site may contain advertising of third parties and links to other sites or frames of other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those third parties or other sites, nor for any third party to whom we transfer your data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

**Consent**

By submitting data to us or our agent or using the Site, you consent to our use of your data in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Copyright**

We have copyright over this Privacy Policy. Use by third parties, even by way of extract, for commercial purposes is not allowed. Infringements may be subject to legal action.

**This Privacy Policy can change at any time to include / exclude clauses and Ethnic Dukaan.com does not bear responsibility for updating users on the same.**

If have questions or doubts regarding our privacy policy, you can contact us.

**Call us** :+91-33-65020250

**Email us** : help@ethnicdukaan.com
